But in mind, this is very popular, especially amongst women.
I'm from Eastern Europe.
Believe me, Slavic women, they're obsessive horoscope.
And we can use it.
We can monetize it.
We can market it on TikTok Instagram and Pinterest.
So how this Kanba extension looks like
when we open a new tab?
Okay, that is a more horoscope flow.
So we can now switch to the one that we like.
For me, it will be, let me see,
can such Gemini tell us a curious species.
Okay, if you're gonna be alone,
there's a person in life we have a like.
And I would just skip it.
And we see some of the information about the horoscope.
And I like it.
It's just very simple, but still 10,000 installations.
So this way, you can pretty much see about lifestyle,
horoscope, and it's changing the news
about the horoscope.
In order to actually use like a famous horoscope,
it's a news like content from Microsoft Start.
We can try to look for some examples, right?
I know there is an interesting app called Starcrowsed.
And we see design here, astrology.
I'll open now a new tab.
I'll actually remove my horoscope from here,
'cause I don't want to use it, but still,
we can kinda get some initial, so we remove it.
And after we remove it and open a new tab,
as you can see, it begs to hacker tap new,
so my previous one.
So this is works well.
We can even install, but I don't need this.
And now I'll open a new project.
I will call it horoscope, a new tab.
Now open a cursor.
How happy that image.
And when I open a cursor, I'll open a folder.
And now go, 'cause I'll sort of give you my other project.
I will go to Chrome extensions.
I will use horoscope new tab.
And first, I will switch to agents.
In agent mouse, I will ask,
I want to create a Chrome extension for horoscope.
Similar to sign,
the ball and that attachment.
It should work as a new tab.
Okay.
And here's similar functionality this to.
And now we'll just copy star cross to solve this.
Okay, and ask it to create it.
You could probably start with total list,
but I think it still will by default create it to a list.
So it will be the current directory and replace a new tab.
We see, okay, it by default is actually creating.
So it's creating new tab.
See, as I'm matching the model design,
and JavaScript, so now it's creating.
I'll post a bit in resume when everything is done.
It's now creating a simple high-complace holder
and updating the money first to handle missing icons
gracefully.
Now enhancing the compatibility metrics
to include all the design combinations.
Okay, the extension is ready to use.
You can test it by loading into a Chrome and opening new tab.
So I will load on packed, go to horoscope new tab.
Okay, we'll not load because not specify icons.
So I will just make a workaround.
The work runs that I won't mouse and it's icons
because for testing purposes.
So I will ask for it because I don't want it.
So it will just remove the references from manifest file.
Okay, now load on packed.
Let me see if now I can install, okay?
I don't actually need to pin it up
because when I open it, as you can see,
it's now keep it.
And now we see the Zodek chart moon,
we see daily horoscope and compatibility.
I think it's a nice start and we will create
additional features in the one of the next episodes.